therandomforest.com 2016-12-25

# Privacy Policy

##  COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

therandomforest.com and our service providers collect the following information from and about you:   
Information from Other Sources. We may supplement the information we collect with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services, commercially available sources and information from our therandomforest.com Affiliates or business partners.   
Information You Submit. You may choose to send us communications through the email addresses listed on the Site or receive newsletters or notifications. Information you submit may include, for example, name, email address, gender and/or zip code.   
Cookies and other tracking technologies such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Site, such as pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run and advertisements you have seen.   
Third parties that support the Site by providing services, such as tracking aggregate Site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. therandomforest.com does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies.   
Activity Information. When you access and interact with the Site, we may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Site, our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Site from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device. At this time we do not respond to browser ‘Do Not Track’ signals, as we await the work of interested stakeholders and others to develop standards for how such signals should be interpreted.   
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content or personalization available through the Site. 

##  INTRODUCTION

This Privacy Policy applies to therandomforest.com collection and use of your personal information i.e., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address. It also describes generally therandomforest.com practices for handling non-personal information for example, interests, demographics and services usage.   
When you visit the Site, you are visiting therandomforest.com corporate website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the websites, mobile applications and other services operated by our Affiliates.   
therandomforest.com or “we” wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information collected through therandomforest.com the “Site”. By using the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.   
The Site is for a general audience, is not targeted to children, and does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. 

##  SECURITY

therandomforest.com uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. However, no one can guarantee the complete safety of your information. 

##  USER ACCESS AND CONTROL

If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact us. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. 

##  OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION

Updates to Privacy Policy. therandomforest.com may modify this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site.   
Linked Services. The Site may also be linked to sites operated by unaffiliated companies, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, newsletters, or applications developed and maintained by unaffiliated companies. therandomforest.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of unaffiliated companies, and once you leave the Site or click an advertisement you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service.   
Data Retention. We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law.   
It is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information due to technical constraints, contractual, financial or legal requirements.   
Sensitive Information. We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal information such as social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership on or through the Site or otherwise. 

##  USE AND DISCLOSURE

We use the information we collect from and about you for these additional purposes:   
We use the information we collect from and about you to provide the Site and features to you, including: to measure and improve those Site and features; to improve your experience with the Site by providing content you may find relevant and interesting; to provide you with support and to respond to inquiries. When the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person, we may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties.   
To allow service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Site. therandomforest.com may make your information available to certain third-party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Site.   
To protect the rights of therandomforest.com and others. There may be instances when therandomforest.com may disclose your information, including situations where therandomforest.com has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: i protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of therandomforest.com, our therandomforest.com Affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use; ii protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the Site or members of the public; iii protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; iv comply with the law or legal process; or v respond to requests from public and government authorities.   
To contact you. therandomforest.com may periodically send materials and notifications related to the Site. If you want to stop receiving materials and notifications, you can contact us by following the unsubscribe instructions that may appear in such communications. There are certain service notification communications that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the Site or policies.   
To share with our therandomforest.com Affiliates. therandomforest.com may share your information with therandomforest.com Affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Users who visit therandomforest.com Affiliates’ services should still refer to their separate privacy policies, which may differ from this Privacy Policy.   
To complete a merger or sale of assets. If therandomforest.com sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, therandomforest.com may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction. 

##  CONTACT US

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:   
Email: privacypolicy@therandomforest.com
